And today, we're going to talk about how to self publish your own comic or graphic novel.
So, are comics really like movies?
Obviously, there have been any number of successful comic movies lately, and they certainly have some things in common.
Comics are a visual medium and movies tend to be a visual medium as well.
Although as we said, with comics you have an unlimited special effects budget.
But, the thing to remember about comics is that they're also a literary medium.
With comics, you have time and you can control the pacing.
It's, it's not like a movie where you're, you're paying for every single minute.
And, if you want to do a voice over and include captions, that's fairly easy to do.
You know, here we've had four pages in a row that are captioned.
You would rarely, if ever, see in a movie where there would have that much voice over time.
Comics are also a literary medium.
You're not doing an inferior job as a comic storyteller to use that and to allow yourself to get inside the comic character's head.